// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "He is fully contented _____ his life.",
    answer: "with",
    options: [
      "of",
      "with",
      "for",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Aqsa is travelling __________ the school.",
    answer: "towards",
    options: [
      "off",
      "to",
      "towards",
      "through"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "You canâ€™t always pass ______ appearance.",
    answer: "By",
    options: [
      "Down",
      "By",
      "Into",
      "Of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "As ____ me; I will be happy to lend a hand?",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "of",
      "in",
      "about",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "We arrived ____ the station an hour late?",
    answer: "at",
    options: [
      "of",
      "in",
      "about",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "She is jealous ____ my friend?",
    answer: "Of",
    options: [
      "From",
      "With",
      "Of",
      "By"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The book is ____ the mug and pen.",
    answer: "Between",
    options: [
      "In",
      "Among",
      "Between",
      "Of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The same considerations are equally applicable ____ accident claims?",
    answer: "To",
    options: [
      "with",
      "To",
      "on",
      "of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "He was upbraided _______ his slovenly appearance?",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "from",
      "for",
      "with",
      "to"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Translate this passage ____ English.",
    answer: "into",
    options: [
      "to",
      "in",
      "into",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Either Sana or her friends ____ present there.",
    answer: "were",
    options: [
      "was",
      "were",
      "is",
      "none"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Do you mean to say you exchanged that lovely car ____ this?",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "with",
      "on",
      "by",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Sana is different _____ other girls.",
    answer: "from",
    options: [
      "than",
      "with",
      "from",
      "to"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "He always insisted ____ his opinion.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [
      "to",
      "in",
      "on",
      "over"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The shopkeeper has charged me ten rupees ____ this book.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "at",
      "with",
      "for",
      "of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "He is getting out ____ the car.",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "from",
      "to",
      "of",
      "through"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Both parties must adhere ____ the terms of the contract.",
    answer: "To",
    options: [
      "In",
      "By",
      "On",
      "To"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "He was accused ____ theft?",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "of",
      "in",
      "about",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "I am good ____ tennis?",
    answer: "at",
    options: [
      "of",
      "in",
      "about",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Turn left ____ the traffic lights.",
    answer: "At",
    options: [
      "At",
      "In",
      "On",
      "Of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "A good judge never jumps ____ the conclusion.",
    answer: "To",
    options: [
      "In",
      "To",
      "on",
      "At"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Parents expect more ____ their children?",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "with",
      "of",
      "from",
      "to"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "He took his brother ____ the hand.",
    answer: "by",
    options: [
      "from",
      "with",
      "on",
      "by"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "He succeeded ____ killing the tiger.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "by",
      "with",
      "of",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "We congratulate you ____ your achievement.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [
      "for",
      "to",
      "on",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "When the meeting had finished, they went ____ the plan once again.",
    answer: "over",
    options: [
      "down",
      "on",
      "up",
      "over"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "I am going ____ home.",
    answer: "None",
    options: [
      "at",
      "to",
      "towards",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "He accused the man ____ stealing.",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "for",
      "on",
      "with",
      "of"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Mother was aware ____ her children.",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "at",
      "of",
      "over",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "He is fond ____ drawing.",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "to",
      "of",
      "with",
      "on"
    ]
  }
];
